# Hoi Man Yuen

Nationality: British

Contact Details: 07732 290428 | hoiman.k.yuen@gmail.com

London SE13 Address:

#### PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

I am a Unity developer and programmer with over 4 years of experience designing and developing video games and interactive edutainment software using C# and Unity3D. From system and game design, graphics, development, and UI/UX to testing, my training in Computer Science, multidisciplinary knowledge and problem-solving skills enable me to take on most tasks independently or as part of a team. Still, I am eager to learn and improve on my expertise, and I aim to further progress into the video game industry.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

#### R&D Engineer / Software Developer at Hactis Ltd., Hong Kong

08/2019 - 03/2023

- Initiated, researched, designed, led and developed a general-purpose multiplayer VR content builder using Unity3D and C#
- Developed various VR gamified interactive applications using Unity3D and C#
- Developed multiple UI and visual enhancements for existing and new VR solutions by creating procedurally generated graphics and shaders
- Increase development efficiency by developing abstraction tools and reusable plugins

#### Summer Internship at Versitech Ltd., Hong Kong

06/2018 - 08/2018

- Developed an AR FPS minigame and a VR matching game for exhibition booths using Unity3D and C#
  - Provided multiple game design proposals according to requirements
  - Performed research and provided solutions to account for resource constraints
  - Implemented game designs into completed products
  - Conduct tests to ensure product quality and user experience

### Game Programmer at Uniques Digital Game Ltd., Hong Kong

09/2014 - 07/2015

- Developed new mechanics for a mobile game using Unity3D and C# (Naval Front-line)
  - Implemented new input system and gameplay elements
  - Designed and implemented new gameplay content and levels
  - Conducted tests and maintenance on existing game systems

### Game Developer (Part-time) at Memoriki Ltd., Hong Kong

04/2014 - 07/2014

- Developed new mobile games using Unity3D and C#
  - Developed related utility GUI programs using C#
  - Provided designs used in game development

## **OTHER PROJECTS**

- Work-in-progress game prototype at <a href="https://github.com/hoimankvuen/DicingHeros">https://github.com/hoimankvuen/DicingHeros</a>
  - A turn-based strategy game with physics about dice
- Experimental game prototype at https://github.com/hoimankyuen/PlaneTactics
  - A turn-based gridless strategy game about plane battles
- University game project showcase at <a href="https://innowings.engg.hku.hk/club-grenade/">https://innowings.engg.hku.hk/club-grenade/</a>
  - A multiplayer lite action game about defeating enemies with grenades

### LANGUAGE AND TECHNICAL SKILLS

**Programming Language:** C#. C++

**Programming IDE:** Visual Studio Operating System: Microsoft Windows

**Version Control System:** GIT

**Software & Tools:** Unity3D, Adobe Photoshop, Blender

Written & Spoken Languages: English, Chinese (written), Cantonese (spoken), Japanese

### **EDUCATION**

The University of Hong Kong, Hong Kong

2015 - 2019

Bachelor of Engineering, Major in Computer Science

School of Continuing and Professional Studies, CUHK, Hong Kong

2012 - 2014

Higher Diploma Programme in Computer Game Development